{
  "LevelId": 64,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 650,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "EFFEMINIZE",
      "question": "process of making someone or something more feminine,"
    },
    {
      "id": 651,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "BLACKCOCKS",
      "question": "hen is known for its predominantly black plumage"
    },
    {
      "id": 652,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "BHIKKHUNIS",
      "question": "female Buddhist monastics who have taken full ordination"
    },
    {
      "id": 653,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "INTERMEZZI",
      "question": "Italian word \"intermezzo,\" often used in music to refer to short,"
    },
    {
      "id": 654,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "COHERENCES",
      "question": "the word \"coherence,\" representing the quality of being logically consistent"
    },
    {
      "id": 655,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CHIFFCHAFF",
      "question": "small, insect-eating bird known for its distinctive \"chiff-chaff\" call,"
    },
    {
      "id": 656,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "FABULATION",
      "question": "literary genre that involves the use of storytelling and inventive narrative techniques"
    },
    {
      "id": 657,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "VALLECULAR",
      "question": "anatomical term for the small, bowl-shaped depression or groove,"
    },
    {
      "id": 658,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "VALLEYLIKE",
      "question": "describes a geographical feature resembling a valley,"
    },
    {
      "id": 659,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "BICYCLIST",
      "question": "an individual who engages in the activity of riding a two-wheeled vehicle"
    },
    {
      "id": 660,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "FAITHFULLY",
      "question": "who consistently and steadfastly adheres to their commitments"
    }
  ]
}